Guide to the Turkish Photography Collection 1910-1990 AD.MC.007
AbuDhabi
- A little girl in a striped dress with a white bow in her hair. 13.4 x 8.5 cm, 16 February 1943; Studio Foto Etem, Ankara, Turkey (Box 7, Folder 7)
  Ankara, Turkey; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkish Writing
- A man and a woman in formal dress standing in front of a large flower arrangement. 14.0 x 8.7 cm, 15 September 1970; Studio Ocak, Turkey (Box 7, Folder 7)
  Flowers; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkey; Turkish Writing; Women
- A young man in a suit with a stern look on his face. 13.6 x 8.5 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 7, Folder 7)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Suits; Turkey; Turkish Writing
- A woman in a bridal gown, sitting in a chair next to three men in suits. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, 26 April 1954; Unknown (Box 7, Folder 7)
  Brides; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Turkish Writing; Wedding Ceremony; Wedding Dresses; Wedding Veils
- A small group of three women, a man and a child, standing in a hallway. 9.0 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 7, Folder 7)
  Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Turkish Writing; Women
- A group of men with two women standing outside a building. 9.0 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Fozturk, Turkey (Box 7, Folder 7)
  Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Trees; Turkey; Women
- A group of thirteen little girls, in three rows, inside a house. 8.5 x 13.6 cm, 25 April 1944; Unknown (Box 7, Folder 7)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Photographic Prints; Radios; Turkey; Turkish Writing
- A large family group with a bride and groom at the center. 8.9 x 14.0 cm, 16 August 1956; Unknown (Box 7, Folder 7)
  Brides; Family; Gelatin Silver Prints; Grooms; Men; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Turkish Writing; Wedding Dresses; Wedding Portraits; Wedding Veils; Women
- A woman sitting in a chair with a young man in a three piece suit behind her. 8.2 x 10.9 cm, 1922; Unknown (Box 7, Folder 8)
  Boys; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Ottoman; Photographic Prints; Photographs; Potted Plants; Suits; Turkey; Women
- A man and a woman with a young girl. 8.8 x 13.8 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Evi, Turkey (Box 7, Folder 8)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Men; Ottoman Writing; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkey; Women
- A group of young men, half in athletic clothes and the other half in suits on a sports field. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, 30 April 1931; Unknown (Box 7, Folder 8)
  Athletes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Sports; Suits; Turkey; Turkish Writing
- A group of men standing around a table eating and drinking. 8.9 x 14.1 cm, 14 January 1972; Studio Sen, Uskadar, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 7, Folder 8)
  Drinking; Eating; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Istanbul, Turkey; Men; Photographic Prints; Suits; Turkish Writing
- Four women and a man sitting behind a table. 8.5 x 13.1 cm, 28 March 1942; Studio Foto Saft Film (Box 7, Folder 8)
  Drinking; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkey; Women
- A young couple holding a baby in a light-colored coat. 8.6 x 13.5 cm, 15 March 1940; Studio Foto M. Fevzi, North Nicosia (Lefkoşa), Cyprus (Box 7, Folder 8)
  Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; North Nicosia (Lefkoşa), Cyprus; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkish Writing; Women
- A couple dancing. 7.0 x 12.4 cm, Undated; Studio Sedat, Bursa, Turkey (Box 7, Folder 8)
  Bursa, Turkey; Couple; Dancing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- Two women, with a young girl and a man in military uniform. 8.7 x 13.4 cm, 2 April 1958; Studio Foto Supham, Van, Turkey (Box 7, Folder 8)
  Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Men; Military; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkish Writing; Uniforms; Van, Turkey; Women
- A large group of men and women, in a banquet hall, sitting at tables or on the floor. 8.1 x 13.9 cm, 1971; Unknown (Box 7, Folder 8)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Smoking; Turkey; Turkish Writing; Women
- A small family group with two young children. 8.5 x 13.3 cm, 1951; Unknown (Box 7, Folder 8)
  Children; Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkey; Turkish Writing; Women
- A large multi-generational family group having a picnic. 8.9 x 14.0 cm, 1949; Unknown (Box 7, Folder 9)
  Children; Countryside; Drinking; Eating; Family; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Picnic; Turkey; Turkish Writing; Women
- A couple, with a young girl in-between them. 8.7 x 13.3 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Sen, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 7, Folder 9)
  Couple; Eye Glasses & Sunglasses; Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Istanbul, Turkey; Mustaches; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- A group of ten young men in military uniform with rifles. 8.9 x 14.0 cm, 6 October 1933; Unknown (Box 7, Folder 9)
  Countryside; Gelatin Silver Prints; Guns; Men; Military; Ottoman Writing; Photographic Prints; Swords & Knives; Turkey; Uniforms
- A large group of school girls in white dresses. 8.8 x 13.8 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 7, Folder 9)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Photographic Prints; Schools; Turkey; Turkish Writing; Uniforms
- A large group of young and older men, some in suits, some in military uniforms outside a wooden building. 8.8 x 14.0 cm, 28 April 1954; Unknown (Box 7, Folder 9)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Military; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Turkish Writing; Uniforms
- A group of men in suits, with a young boy posing in a dirt lot. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, 29 March 1934; Studio Foto Ahmet Hulusi, Boyabat, Sinop, Turkey (Box 7, Folder 9)
  Boys; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Sinop, Turkey; Studio Photography; Suits; Turkish Writing
- A seated bride with family members around her in front of a mirror. 8.4 x 13.3 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Luks, Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 7, Folder 9)
  Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey; Brides; Family; Flowers; Gelatin Silver Prints; Jewelry; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Wedding Dresses; Wedding Veils
- Six women wearing cardigans or jackets. 8.2 x 13.6 cm, 21 February 1950; Unknown (Box 7, Folder 9)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Jewelry; Makeup; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Turkish Writing; Women
- Three men in suits, seated around a table with food and drink on it. 8.4 x 13.5 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Hikmet, Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 7, Folder 9)
  Alcohol; Drinking; Food; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Restaurants; Studio Photography; Turkey
- A family group of six, with an older male in traditional dress with a walking stick. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 7, Folder 9)
  Canes & Walking Sticks; Children; Family; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Ottoman Writing; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Women
- A young bride surrounded by family members. 8.6 x 13.4 cm, 26 September 1951; Studio Foto Pastel (Box 7, Folder 10)
  Family; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Turkish Writing; Wedding Dresses; Wedding Veils
- A large group of men women and children, in front of a large mountain range. 8.7 x 13.8 cm, 26 June 1933; Unknown (Box 7, Folder 10)
  Children; Erzincan, Turkey; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Mountains; Photographic Prints; Turkish Writing; Women
- Two older women in dark dresses. 8.7 x 13.8 cm, 1 January 1930; Unknown (Box 7, Folder 10)
  Armenian Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Women
- Five men in military uniform, standing next to a man in an officer's uniform. 8.7 x 13.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 7, Folder 10)
  Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Military; Officers; Photographic Prints; Trees; Turkey; Uniforms
- A couple, posing with a naked baby. 8.8 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 7, Folder 10)
  Children; Couple; Gelatin Silver Prints; Naked; Ottoman Writing; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- A family group of four, eating at the dinner table. 8.7 x 14.0 cm, 3 November 1956; Unknown (Box 7, Folder 10)
  Drinking; Eating; Family; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Turkish Writing
- A large family group in the living room with men, women and children. 8.8 x 13.4 cm, 23-24 February 1953; Unknown (Box 7, Folder 10)
  Children; Family; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Turkish Writing; Women
- Four young men in suits and ties, seated around a table with an ashtray filled with cigarettes on it. 8.4 x 13.4 cm, 1946; Studio Foto Model, Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 7, Folder 10)
  Armenian Writing; Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey; Cigarettes; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Suits
- A small family group of three adults and one small baby. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, 31 December 1936; Studio Foto Palas, Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 7, Folder 10)
- A group of women on a corniche with a navy ship in the background. 8.8 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Karliova, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 7, Folder 10)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Seas; Ships; Studio Photography; Trees; Women
- A middle aged couple, male is wearing a military uniform. 8.4 x 13.7 cm, 26 September 1941; Unknown (Box 7, Folder 11)
  Ankara, Turkey; Couple; Gelatin Silver Prints; Military; Photographic Prints; Turkish Writing; Uniforms
- A group of five women sitting at a table in a restaurant. Marmara Lokali. 8.7 x 13.9 cm, 2 December 1949; Unknown (Box 7, Folder 11)
  Flowers; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Restaurants; Turkey; Turkish Writing; Women
- A young couple, holding a little girl, man is wearing a military uniform. 8.8 x 13.7 cm, 21 January 1942; Unknown (Box 7, Folder 11)
  Couple; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Military; Photographic Prints; Toys; Turkey; Turkish Writing; Uniforms
- A group of women of varing ages, eating and drinking at a long table. 8.3 x 13.3 cm, 1958; Unknown (Box 7, Folder 11)
  Armenian Writing; Drinking; Eating; Gelatin Silver Prints; Nurses; Photographic Prints; Restaurants; Turkey; Women
- A group of nine men in military uniform with backpacks on. 8.7 x 14.0 cm, 27 [-?-] 1939; Unknown (Box 7, Folder 11)
  Cigarettes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Military; Photographic Prints; Smoking; Swords & Knives; Turkey; Turkish Writing; Uniforms
- Two young women with dark jackets in front of a painted backdrop. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, 21 February 1939; Unknown (Box 7, Folder 11)
  Amasya, Turkey; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Turkish Writing
- A group of six men and women at a dinner table drinking wine. 8.5 x 13.5 cm, Undated; Studio Alim Urus, Izmir, Turkey (Box 7, Folder 11)
  Alcohol; Drinking; Gelatin Silver Prints; Izmir, Turkey; Men; Photographic Prints; Women
- A small family group of five, with a young man in uniform and an older woman with a head cover. 8.8 x 13.6 cm, 1949; Studio Foto Kontaks, Sofia, Bulgaria.; Unknown (Box 7, Folder 11)
  Cyrillic Writing; Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Head Covers; Men; Military; Photographic Prints; Sofia, Bulgaria; Uniforms; Women
- Spectators at the Republic Day celebrations on a large field. 8.8 x 12.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 7, Folder 11)
  Ceremony; Children; Countryside; Flags; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Officials; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Turkish Writing; Women
- A large family group sitting at a table with an ashtray on it. 8.5 x 12.2 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Naci (Box 7, Folder 11)
  Children; Cigarettes; Fashion Accessories; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkey; Women
- A mixed family group gathered around a bride and groom holding flowers. 8.8 x 13.7 cm, 3 September 1954; Studio Serengil, Kadikoy, Turkey (Box 7, Folder 12)
  Brides; Family; Flowers; Gelatin Silver Prints; Grooms; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Wedding Dresses; Wedding Portraits; Wedding Veils
- A small family group with two young men in military uniforms and a woman with a head cover. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, 3 June 1910; Sebah & Joaillier, Pera, Constantinople (Box 7, Folder 12)
  Boys; Constantinople; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Military; Ottoman Writing; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkey; Uniforms; Veils; Women
- A large mixed group, with a bride, standing in front of a large trophy case. 8.4 x 13.6 cm, 20 January 1955; Unknown (Box 7, Folder 12)
  Brides; Family; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Turkish Writing; Wedding Ceremony; Wedding Dresses; Wedding Veils; Women
- A young bride and a groom in a military uniform. 8.8 x 13.9 cm, 19 July 1934; Studio Turk Fotograf Evi, Turkey (Box 7, Folder 12)
  Brides; Gelatin Silver Prints; Grooms; Military; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkey; Turkish Writing; Uniforms; Wedding Dresses; Wedding Portraits; Wedding Veils
- A group of school children sitting at their desks with a Santa Claus carrying a sack of toys in the back of the room. 8.8 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Studio Ali, Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 7, Folder 12)
  Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Mustafa Kemal Ataturk, 1881-1938; Photographic Prints; Santa Claus; Schools; Students; Studio Photography; Uniforms
- A large family group gathered under streamers and in front of a tapestry of the Kaaba. 9.1 x 13.8 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 7, Folder 12)
  Children; Circumcisions; Gelatin Silver Prints; Ka'aba, Mecca, Saudi Arabia; Men; Party; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Turkish Writing; Women
- A group of men in military uniforms on a ship. 8.8 x 13.8 cm, 9 January 1931; Unknown (Box 7, Folder 12)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Istanbul, Turkey; Men; Military; Newspapers; Photographic Prints; Turkish Writing; Uniforms
- A family group of two older women, three female children and one boy. 8.4 x 13.2 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Ankara, Ankara, Turkey (Box 7, Folder 12)
  Ankara, Turkey; Boys; Children; Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Head Covers; Photographic Prints; Turkish Writing; Women
- A large group of school aged boys in suits posing outside. 8.8 x 13.9 cm, 1930; Unknown (Box 7, Folder 12)
  Boys; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Students; Suits; Turkey; Turkish Writing
- A man in a suit standing with seven young girls, wearing medals. 8.2 x 13.2 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Enstanta, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 7, Folder 12)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Istanbul, Turkey; Men; Photographic Prints; Sports; Studio Photography
- A couple, man in a military uniform, woman wearing a necklace and a see-through top. 8.4 x 13.0 cm, Undated; Studio Turk Fotograf Evi, Turkey (Box 7, Folder 13)
  Couple; Gelatin Silver Prints; Jewelry; Military; Ottoman Writing; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkey; Uniforms
- A group of adults in fancy dress and suits inside a house, with food and drinks. 8.8 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Studio Site Fotograf Ajansi, Ankara, Turkey (Box 7, Folder 13)
  Ankara, Turkey; Drinking; Eating; Formal Dress; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Suits; Women
- A large family group surrounding a bride and groom, groom is wearing a military uniform. 8.4 x 13.7 cm, Undated; Studio Hamza Rustem Ali Balim, Izmir, Turkey (Box 7, Folder 13)
  Brides; Children; Family; Gelatin Silver Prints; Grooms; Izmir, Turkey; Men; Military; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Uniforms; Wedding Dresses; Wedding Portraits; Wedding Veils; Women
- A man in a suit with his hands on the shoulders of two women. 8.6 x 13.4 cm, 17 September 1944; Studio Hamza Rustem Ali Balim, Izmir, Turkey (Box 7, Folder 13)
  Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Izmir, Turkey; Men; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkish Writing; Women
- A group of school aged boys, sitting at a long dining table, with an older man in the background. 9.0 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Senel, Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 7, Folder 13)
  Armenian Writing; Boys; Drinking; Eating; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Schools; Students; Studio Photography; Suits; Turkey
- Two young girls with short hair and sweaters, leaning on a railing. 8.7 x 13.6 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 7, Folder 13)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Houses; Ottoman Writing; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- Six young women with three young children, one is holding a ball. 9.0 x 14.0 cm, 31 May 1935; Studio Foto Lutfu (Box 7, Folder 13)
  Boys; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Houses; Photographic Prints; Toys; Turkey; Turkish Writing; Women
- A family group of five, of three women and two men. 9.1 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Studio Serengil, Kadikoy, Turkey (Box 7, Folder 13)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Istanbul, Turkey; Men; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkish Writing; Women
- A couple, woman is wearing jewelry. 8.8 x 12.7 cm, 22 December 1957; Studio Resat, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 7, Folder 13)
  Couple; Gelatin Silver Prints; Istanbul, Turkey; Jewelry; Makeup; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Suits; Turkish Writing
- A large family group, surrounding a bride and groom, in military uniform, in front of a mirror. 8.8 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 7, Folder 13)
  Brides; Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Grooms; Military; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Turkish Writing; Uniforms; Wedding Portraits
- An older woman sitting on the beach in her bathing suit. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, 5 August 1955; Studio Foto Cumhuriyet, Taksim, Turkey (Box 7, Folder 14)
  Bathing Suits; Beaches; Gelatin Silver Prints; Istanbul, Turkey; Ottoman Writing; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
- A 1939-1940 Izmit junior high school volleyball team and their coach. 8.8 x 13.9 cm, 25 April 1940; Unknown (Box 7, Folder 14)
  Athletes; Boys; Gelatin Silver Prints; Kocaeli, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Schools; Sports
- A group a five young girls. 8.6 x 13.8 cm, 8 February 1963; Studio Foto Ifa, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 7, Folder 14)
  French Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
- A group of five young men sitting around a table, one is lighting a cigarette. 9.1 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Istiklab (Box 7, Folder 14)
  Cigarettes; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Istanbul, Turkey; Men; Photographic Prints; Smoking; Studio Photography; Suits
- A large family group with a bride and two older women with head covers. 8.9 x 14.1 cm, 6 February 1948; Unknown (Box 7, Folder 14)
  Brides; Children; Family; Gelatin Silver Prints; Head Covers; Men; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Turkish Writing; Wedding Portraits; Women
- A family group of five, a young girl is holding a large bouquet of flowers. 8.8 x 14.2 cm, Undated; Studio Fotograf Ajansi, Kizilay, Turkey (Box 7, Folder 14)
  Ankara, Turkey; Boys; Flowers; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Head Covers; Men; Photographic Prints; Turkish Writing; Women
- A group of six men, in military uniform eating and smoking. 9.1 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 7, Folder 14)
  Eating; Eye Glasses & Sunglasses; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Military; Photographic Prints; Smoking; Turkey; Turkish Writing; Uniforms
- A group of five men in suits, standing in front of a sheer curtain. 9.0 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 7, Folder 14)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Suits; Turkey; Turkish Writing
- A man in a double breasted jacket, leaning on a car with two boys in the car. 8.8 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Studio Ramiz Goksay, Izmir, Turkey (Box 7, Folder 14)
  Boys; Cars; Gelatin Silver Prints; Izmir, Turkey; Men; Photographic Prints
- A family group of six, standing in the front yard of a house. Cinarcik, Yalova. 9.0 x 14.0 cm, 27 August 1969; Unknown (Box 7, Folder 14)
  Eye Glasses & Sunglasses; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Houses; Men; Photographic Prints; Turkish Writing; Women; Yalova, Turkey
- Two young boys playing football in the street. 9.0 x 14.0 cm, 1929; Unknown (Box 7, Folder 15)
  Boys; Bursa, Turkey; Footballs; Gelatin Silver Prints; Ottoman Writing; Photographic Prints; Sports
- Three men in lab coats working in a chemistry lab. 9.4 x 12.1 cm, 1949; Unknown (Box 7, Folder 15)
  Chemistry; Gelatin Silver Prints; Izmir, Turkey; Labcoats; Laboratory; Men; Photographic Prints; Schools; Turkish Writing; University
- A large family group, with a bride and groom in the middle. 8.7 x 13.5 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Araz (Box 7, Folder 15)
  Brides; Family; Gelatin Silver Prints; Grooms; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Wedding Ceremony; Wedding Dresses; Wedding Veils
- A group of six women and one man, standing in an art gallery. 9.1 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Hamit Kinayturk, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 7, Folder 15)
  Art; Coats; Drinking; Fashion Accessories; Gelatin Silver Prints; Istanbul, Turkey; Men; Painting; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
- An older couple, with a curtain and a light in the background. Same couple from ref1495. 8.7 x 13.5 cm, 4 June 1954; Studio Foto Sark, Karsiyaka, Turkey (Box 7, Folder 15)
  Couple; Gelatin Silver Prints; Izmir, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkey
- A group of six men and women sitting around a table, eating and drinking. Same couple from ref1494. 8.5 x 13.6 cm, Undated; Studio Alim Urus, Izmir, Turkey (Box 7, Folder 15)
  Drinking; Eating; Gelatin Silver Prints; Izmir, Turkey; Men; Photographic Prints; Restaurants; Studio Photography; Women
- Three men in hats, sitting around the edge of a fountain. 8.9 x 12.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 7, Folder 15)
  Coats; Gelatin Silver Prints; Hats; Men; Photographic Prints; Soldiers; Turkey; Turkish Writing
- A group of men and women sitting around a small table with drinks on it. 8.5 x 13.0 cm, 31 January 1948; Studio Foto Nur, Karsiyaka, Turkey (Box 7, Folder 15)
  Drinking; Gelatin Silver Prints; Izmir, Turkey; Men; Photographic Prints; Restaurants; Studio Photography; Turkish Writing; Women
- A man sitting a desk, smoking with another man lighting his cigarette and the other holding paperwork for him to sign. 8.9 x 11.8 cm, Undated; Studio Turkiye Basin Foto Ajansi, Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 7, Folder 15)
  Cigarettes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Offices; Photographic Prints; Smoking; Turkey
- A group of boys and girls of varying ages with flower arrangements. 8.6 x 13.4 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Ileri, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 7, Folder 15)
  Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey; Boys; Ceremony; Flowers; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- A couple, looking off camera. 8.8 x 13.6 cm, Undated; Studio Tanju, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 7, Folder 16)
- A man sitting at a desk, counting money. 8.6 x 13.7 cm, 7 January 1953; Studio Ramiz Goksay, Izmir, Turkey (Box 7, Folder 16)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Izmir, Turkey; Men; Offices; Photographic Prints; Shopkeepers; Shops; Studio Photography; Suits
- A group of nine women from the Istanbul Kiz Lisesi (Girls' High School) volleyball team, in sport track suits. 8.8 x 12.6 cm, April 1972; Unknown (Box 7, Folder 16)
  Athletes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Sports; Turkey; Turkish Writing; Women
- A young child sitting on a chair, playing the accordion at a party. 9.0 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Senel, Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 7, Folder 16)
  Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Istanbul, Turkey; Men; Musical Instruments; Party; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
- A couple looking off camera, Bursa. 8.5 x 13.5 cm, 30 August 1946; Studio Foto Ar A. Iyigun, Ankara, Turkey (Box 7, Folder 16)
  Ankara, Turkey; Couple; Gelatin Silver Prints; Jewelry; Makeup; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkish Writing